Guide to the Clubs, Societies, and Organizations at Yale Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Clubs, societies, and organizations at Yale records
1768-2006
RU 56
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
39.33
(75 boxes)
The records consist of minutes of meetings, membership lists, correspondence, constitutions and bylaws, scrapbooks, library records, financial and business records, programs and invitations, articles and news clippings, reports, songbooks, notices, newsletters, and related materials documenting the organization, activities, and operations of various student, faculty, and staff organizations, and other Yale community groups.
Acacia Fraternity. Yale Chapter
Alpha Delta Phi. Yale Chapter
Beaumont Medical Club
Beta Theta Pi. Phi Chi Chapter (Yale University)
Centro Español de Yale
Chi Epsilon (U.S.)
Chi Phi (Fraternity). Omicron Chapter (Yale University)
Delta Kappa Epsilon. Phi Chapter (Yale University)
Delta Phi. Omicron Chapter (Yale University)
Faculty Club (New Haven, Conn.)
Kappa Sigma Epsilon (Yale College: 1840-1880)
Moral Society (Yale College)
Phi Gamma Delta. Nu Deuteron Chapter (Yale University)
Phi Sigma Kappa. Epsilon Chapter (Yale University)
Psi Upsilon Fraternity. Beta Chapter (Yale University)
Sigma Lambda Kappa (Yale College)
Society of Brothers in Unity (Yale College)
Theta Nu Epsilon. Lambda Epsilon Chapter (Yale College)
Wigwam Club
Yale Amateurs
Yale College (1718-1887). A. P. Society
Yale College (1718-1887). Atalanta Boat Club
Yale College (1718-1887). Benevolent Society
Yale College (1718-1887). Cymothoe Boat Club
Yale College (1718-1887). Gamma Nu
Yale College (1718-1887). Glyuna Boat Club
Yale College (1718-1887). Phi Epsilon Society
Yale College (1718-1887). Phi Theta Psi
Yale College (1718-1887). Philagorian Society
Yale College (1718-1887). Philencration Society
Yale College (1718-1887). Temperance Society
Yale College (1718-1887). Thulia Club
Yale College (1718-1887). Varuna Boat Club
Yale College (1718-1887). York Street Club
Yale Mineralogical Society
Yale Natural History Society
Yale Society of Civil Engineers
Yale Union Club
Yale University Club
Yale University. Cercle Français
Yale University. Anthropology Club
Yale University. Beethoven Society
Yale University. Chess Club
Yale University. Graduate School. Modern Language Club
Yale University. Hē Boulē
Yale University. Junior Promenade
Yale University. Kappa Psi
Yale University. Kappa Sigma Theta
Yale University. Philosophical Club
Yale University. Republican Club
Yale University. Semetic and Biblical Club
Yale University. Sophomore German Committee
Yale University. Student Council
Yale University. Torch and Mask Society
Yale University. Wicket Club
Yale University. Wooden Spoon Exhibition
Yale University. Wurts Debating Club
Yale University. Yale Dames
Yale University. Yale Hebrew Club
Yale University. Yale Italian Society
Yale University. Yale Outing Club
Yale University. Yale Photography Club
Yale University. Yale Political Union
Yale University. Yale University Boat Club
Zeta Psi Fraternity. Eta Chapter (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 40 (YRG 40), Records of Yale clubs, societies, and organizations.
Conditions Governing Access
The records in this collection are partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Existence and Location of Originals
Records for several organizations have been removed from accession 19ND-A-377 and transferred to record units for their appropriate organization.
Records of the Thulia Boat Club, the Varuna Boat Club, the Glyuna Boat Club, and the Yale Navy, 1853-1896, are available on 1 microfilm reel, HM 161.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of minutes of meetings, membership lists, correspondence, constitutions and bylaws, scrapbooks, library records, financial and business records, programs and invitations, certificates, articles and news clippings, reports, songbooks, notices, newsletters, and related materials documenting the organization, activities, and operations of various student, faculty, and staff organizations, and other Yale community groups.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Accession 2018-A-049 transferred from the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, 2018.
College students -- Societies, etc.; College teachers -- Societies, etc.; Greek letter societies; Universities and colleges -- Employees -- Societies, etc.; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Faculty; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Officers and employees; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Societies, etc.; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Students; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Officers and employees; Yale University -- Societies, etc.; Yale University -- Students
- Sigma Lambda Kappa Constitution and correspondence, undated; Accession 19ND-A-055
  - Constitution and correspondence of Sigma Lambda Kappa, Undated (Box 1A)
- Berkeley Players constitution, undated; Accession 19ND-A-064
  - Constitution of the Berkeley Players, Undated (Box 1F)
- Phi Gamma Delta membership certificate, circa 1932; Accession 19ND-A-068
  - Phi Gamma Delta membership certificate of Avard Longley Bishop (1932), circa 1932 (Box 1)
- Yale clubs and organizations, circa 1768-1973; Accession 19ND-A-377
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged alphabetically by organization name.
  In 2008, records for several organizations were transferred from this accession to record units for their appropriate organization.
  - ACACIA CLUB
    - Petition of the Acacia Club for a charter (2 copies), 1906 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ALPHA DELTA PHI
    - Constitution, 1832 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Constitution, amended, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Constitution, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - By-laws of the Yale chapter, 1855 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - By-laws of the Yale chapter; Interpretation of the symbols, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Tyler Trust Association By-laws, 1893 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Tyler Trust-Fund Association Account book and Articles of Association, 1893, 1904-1915 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Tyler Trust Association Record book, 1927-1935 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Account book, 1836-1864 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Ledger, 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder 10a)
    - Convention: thirty-seventh annual, 1869 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Register of delegates, 1850s (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Scrapbook of bill and receipts, 1893-1896 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Playbill of "A Faire Quarell" by Thomas Middleton and William Rowley, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Invitation to initiation, 1856 June 15 (Box 2, Folder 14a)
  - ANTHROPOLOGY CLUB
    - Minutes of meetings, accounts, lists, 1901-1917 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, library certificate, lists, 1903-1916, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - ATALANTA BOAT CLUB
    - Constitution, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - BEAUMONT MEDICAL CLUB Y, 1920
    - Memo re first meeting; Silhouette of Beaumont by B. S. Burr (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - BEETHOVEN SOCIETY
    - Records, 3 vols, 1825-1846 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Statement/petition, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - BENEVOLENT SOCIETY
    - Constitution and minutes; Catalog of members with the amount of their subscriptions, 1813-1823 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Constitution, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Circulation charges, 1841-1851 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Circulation charges, 1852-1861 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Circulation charges, 1861-1876 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Permission to use slips, 1844-1866, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Requests to draw books, 1845-1847 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - BERKELEY COLLEGE PLAYERS
    General note
    Constitution See: Yale Clubs Folio #1
  - BERZELIUS SOCIETY
    See: William -Brewer Papers Ms. #100
  - BOULE, HE
    - Histories (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Constitution, by-laws, calendar, 1887-1903 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1889-1895 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1895-1900 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1900-1902 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Scrapbook pages of mementos, 1890s (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Scrapbook of mementos, 1901-1902 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Scrapbook of mementos, 1878-1903 (Box 7a, Folder 35)
  - BROTHERS IN UNITY
    - Secretary's records
      - Book II, minutes of meetings, 1783-1803 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - Book III, minutes of meetings, 1803-1816 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - Book IV, minutes of meetings; List of Presidents of the Society, 1816-1828, 1768-1852 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - Book V, minutes of meetings, 1828-1840 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - Constitution and meeting minutes, 1783-1803 (Box 8a)
      - constitution, 1831 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Book VI, minutes of meetings, 1840-1851 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Book VII, minutes of meetings and members' lists, 1851-1870 (Box 9, Folder 42)
        General
        See box 19, folder 88.
      - Constitution of the society, printed, 1852 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - petitions and reports, 1825, 1850 (Box 9, Folder 44)
      - catalogue of members, 1768-1845 (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - meeting exercises, 1814-1820 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      - meeting exercises, 1824-1829 (Box 9, Folder 47)
      - catalogue of members and debate topics, 1831-1839 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      - catalogue of members and debate topics, 1840-1856 (Box 10, Folder 49)
      - debate topics, 1862-1869 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Hexahedron Society, The Talebearer, nos. 1-30, 1819 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - valedictory oration by Timothy Mather Cooley, 1792 (Box 10, Folder 52)
      - valedictory orations, 1816-1827 (Box 10, Folder 53)
      - prize debate by Edward Y. Hincks, 1863 (Box 11, Folder 54)
      - prize debates and orations by Anson Phelps Tinker, 1865-1866, undated (Box 11, Folder 55)
      - prize debates and orations by Anson Phelps Tinker, 1867-68, undated (Box 11, Folder 56)
      - compositions by Anson Phelps Tinker, 1857-87, undated (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Treasurer's records
      - account book, 1823-36 (Box 11, Folder 58)
      - account book and list of treasurers, 1849-63 (Box 11, Folder 59)
      - record of contributions, 1853 (Box 11, Folder 60)
      - Reports of the collector, fiscal agent, and treasurer, 1854-84, undated (Box 11, Folder 61)
      - taxes, credit day-book, 1860-1866 (Box 12, Folder 62)
      - Correspondence and receipts re Hopkins Grammar School celebration, 1860 (Box 12, Folder 62a)
      - Tax ledger, classes of 1861-69 [See: box 20, folder 89], 1860-65 (Box 12, Folder 63)
      - Tax ledger, classes of 1861-1871 [See: box 20, folder 90], 1861-1867 (Box 12, Folder 64)
      - Receipts, 1862-1865 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Librarian's records
      - Library catalogue, 1780, 1846 (Box 12, Folder 65a)
      - Library catalogue, 1829-1832 (Box 12, Folder 66)
      - missing books, 1836 (Box 12, Folder 67)
      - added books, 1842 (Box 12, Folder 68)
      - library catalogue, 1837-1838 (Box 12, Folder 69)
      - library catalogue, 1845 (Box 12, Folder 70)
      - reports, 1847-1867 (Box 12, Folder 71)
      - correspondence, 1846 (Box 12, Folder 72)
      - register, 1848-1849 (Box 13, Folder 73)
      - library catalogue, 1848-1849 (Box 13, Folder 74)
      - register, 1850 (Box 13, Folder 75)
      - donations, fines, fees, 1850-1894 (Box 13, Folder 76)
      - register, 1869 (Box 14, Folder 77)
      - memorandum and magazine register, 1859-1886 (Box 14, Folder 78)
      - periodical charges, 1830 (Box 14, Folder 79)
      - circulation charges, 1832-1833 (Box 14, Folder 80)
      - circulation charges, 1833-1835 (Box 14, Folder 81)
      - circulation charges, 1841-1842 (Box 14, Folder 82)
      - circulation charges, 1847-1850 (Box 15, Folder 83)
      - circulation charges, 1850-1855 (Box 15, Folder 84)
      - circulation charges, 1855-1861 (Box 16, Folder 85)
      - circulation charges, 1860-1867 (Box 17, Folder 86)
      - circulation charges and missing books, 1868-1875 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Secretary's records: Book VII, minutes of meetings 6 members lists, 1851-1872 (Box 19, Folder 88)
    - Treasurer's records: tax ledger, classes of 1861-69, 1861-1865 (Box 19, Folder 89)
    - Treasurer's records: tax ledger, classes of 1861-1871, 1861-1867 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - CENTRO ESPANOL
    - Constitution, history, insignia, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 140)
    - Minutes and programs, 1934-1947 (Box 31, Folder 141)
    - Correspondence, 1934, 1947-1948 (Box 31, Folder 142)
    - Financial papers, 1933-1947 (Box 31, Folder 143)
    - Songs (Box 31, Folder 144)
    - Membership lists, 1940-1953 (Box 31, Folder 145)
  - CERCLE FRANCAIS
    - Minutes and roll, 1903-1905 (Box 31, Folder 146)
    - Ledger, 1913-1914 (Box 31, Folder 147)
    - Play: Le Medecin Malgre Lui, directed by B. Hollister, 1905 (Box 31, Folder 148)
  - CHI EPSILON (Box 31, Folder 149)
    - Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 32, Folder 150)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 151)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 32, Folder 152)
    - Constitution, by-laws, policy, Rules, procedures (Box 32, Folder 153)
    - Minutes of meetings, newsletters (Box 32, Folder 154)
    - Conclaves, 1960-1966 (Box 33, Folder 155)
    - Ritual, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 156)
    - Permanent membership records, 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 157)
    - Congratulations to Chi Epsilon, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 158)
    - Articles, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 159)
    - Financial papers, 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 160)
    - Checkbook and ledger, 1955-1958 (Box 33, Folder 161)
    - Guest book; The Transit, 15 issues; Miscellaneous printed items, 1955-1965 (Box 34, Folder 162)
    - Installation, 1956 January 20 (Folder 1E)
  - CHI PHI
    - Emblem (Folder 1D)
  - CIVIL ENGINEERS, YALE SOCIETY OF
    - Minutes of meetings, 1917-1922 (Box 38, Folder 170)
  - CYMOTHOE BOAT CLUB
    - Boat Insurance policy, 1859 (Box 38, Folder 171)
  - DELTA KAPPA
    - Constitution, by-laws, fist of members, 1845-1879 (Box 38, Folder 172)
    - Catalogue of members, 1849-1870 (Box 38, Folder 173)
    - Roll book, 1857-1869 (Box 38, Folder 174)
    - Roll book, 1870-1878 (Box 38, Folder 175)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1862-1863 (Box 39, Folder 176)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1865-1867 (Box 39, Folder 177)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1872-1878 (Box 39, Folder 178)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1851-1855 (Box 39, Folder 179)
  - DELTA KAPPA EPSILON
    - Minutes of meetings, 1853-1862 (Box 39, Folder 180)
    - Correspondence
      - A-C (Box 40, Folder 181)
      - D-J (Box 40, Folder 182)
      - K-M (Box 40, Folder 183)
      - N-Z (Box 40, Folder 184)
    - James J. Hogan Memorial Scholarship Fund, treasurer of committee; history and poetry, Undated (Box 41, Folder 185)
  - DELTA PHI
    - History of the Omicron Chapter, Undated (Box 41, Folder 186)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1925-1932 (Box 41, Folder 187)
  - ECONOMICS CLUB
    - Minutes of meetings (as Political Science Club), 1886-1898 (Box 41, Folder 188)
    - Minutes of meetings, 2 vols., 1899-1920 (Box 41, Folder 189)
  - EPSILON ASSOCIATION
    - Legal papers, circa 1905-1906 (Box 41, Folder 190)
  - ETA PHI
    - Constitution and by-laws, 3 vols., 1882-1900 (Box 42, Folder 191)
    - Constitution and member lists, 1882-1907 (Box 42, Folder 192)
    - Minutes, 2 vols., 1879-1883 (Box 42, Folder 193)
    - Minutes, 1883-1886 (Box 42, Folder 194)
    - Minutes, 2 vols., 1886-1892 (Box 43, Folder 195)
    - Minutes, 2 vols., 1892-1896 (Box 43, Folder 196)
    - Minutes, 2 vols., 1897-1903 (Box 43, Folder 197)
    - Minutes, 1900 (Box 43, Folder 198)
    - Roll call, 1889-1897 (Box 43, Folder 199)
    - Treasurer"s book, 1881-1885 (Box 43, Folder 200)
    - Treasurer"s books, 2 vols., 1885-1893 (Box 44, Folder 201)
    - Play Committee: notebooks, 1891, 1900 (Box 44, Folder 202)
  - GAMMA MU
    - Constitution and treasurer"s accounts; constitution and bylaws, 1861-1870, 1860 (Box 53, Folder 241)
  - GLYUNA BOAT CLUB
    - Constitution, lists of members, 1860 (Box 53, Folder 250)
    - Receipts, 1860-1866 (Box 53, Folder 251)
  - HALCYON BOAT CLUB
    - Constitution, Undated (Box 53, Folder 252)
  - HEBREW CLUB
    - Records, 1890-1891 (Box 53, Folder 253)
  - JUNIOR PROMENADE COMMITTEE
    - Notebook, 1893 (Box 53, Folder 254)
    - Correspondence, 1929-1930 (Box 53, Folder 255)
  - KAPPA PSI
    - Records, 1900-1902 (Box 54, Folder 256)
    - Constitution and by-laws, 1896-1905 (Box 54, Folder 257)
  - KAPPA SIGMA EPSILON
    - Records, 1844-1847 (Box 54, Folder 258)
    - Records, 1847-1855 (Box 54, Folder 259)
  - KAPPA SIGMA THETA
    - Constitution and by-laws, 1857 (Box 55, Folder 260)
    - Records, 1845-1848 (Box 55, Folder 261)
    - Records, 1850-1857 (Box 55, Folder 262)
  - KNIGHTS OF THE ROUND TABLE
    - Constitution, by-laws and members, Undated (Box 56, Folder 263)
  - MINERALOGICAL SOCIETY
    - Constitution and by-laws, Undated (Box 55, Folder 264)
  - MODERN LANGUAGE: CLUB
    - Records, constitution, 1891-1895 (Box 56, Folder 265)
    - Records, 1895-1906 (Box 56, Folder 266)
    - Records, 1906-1915 (Box 56, Folder 267)
  - MORAL SOCIETY
    - Library records, 1819-1823 (Box 57, Folder 268)
    - Library records, 1824-1827 (Box 57, Folder 269)
    - Library records, 1828-1831 (Box 57, Folder 270)
    - Library records, 1832-1840 (Box 57, Folder 271)
    - Library records, 1841-1844 (Box 57, Folder 272)
    - Library catalogue, 1845-1850 (Box 58, Folder 273)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1797-1819 (Box 58, Folder 274)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1820-1841 (Box 58, Folder 275)
    - Constitution and members, also contains the constitution of the Rhetorical Society, 1834 (Box 58, Folder 276)
    - Treasurer"s book, 1831-1832 (Box 58, Folder 277)
  - ORIENTAL CLUB OF NEW HAVEN
    - Constitution and minutes, 1913-1948 (Box 59, Folder 278)
    - Minutes, 1948-1972 (Box 59, Folder 279)
  - PHI EPSILON SOCIETY
    - Records and miscellaneous material, 1837-1839 (Box 59, Folder 280)
  - PHI GAMMA DELTA
    - Correspondence, 1910-1918 (Box 59, Folder 281)
  - PHI THETA PSI
    - Records, 1864-1866 (Box 59, Folder 282)
  - PHILAGORIAN SOCIETY
    - Constitution and records, 1828-1830 (Box 60, Folder 283)
  - PHILENCRATIAN SOCIETY
    - Constitution, members, and records, 1827-1830 (Box 60, Folder 284)
  - PHILOCRATION SOCIETY
    - Oration upon its dissolution, Junius Y. Smith, 1800 (Box 60, Folder 285)
  - PHILOSOPHICAL CLUB
    - Minutes, 1887-1891 (Box 60, Folder 286)
    - Minutes, 1896-1908 (Box 60, Folder 287)
  - PHOTOGRAPHY CLUB
    - History, 1943 (Box 60, Folder 288)
  - PSI UPSILON
    - Records, vol. I, 1839-1850 (Box 61, Folder 289)
    - Records, vol. II, 1850-1854 (Box 61, Folder 290)
    - Records, vol. III, 1855-1863 (Box 61, Folder 291)
    - Records, vol. IV, 1863-1869 (Box 62, Folder 292)
    - Records, vol. V, 1870-1875 (Box 62, Folder 293)
    - Correspondence, 1872 (Box 62, Folder 293a)
    - Records, vol. VI, 1884 (Box 62, Folder 294)
    - Treasury book, 1839-1867 (Box 63, Folder 295)
  - RHETORICAL SOCIETY
    See: Box 58 Folder 276 of the Moral Society
  - SEMITIC AND BIBLICAL CLUB
    - Records, vol. I, 1887-1913 (Box 64, Folder 297)
    - Records, vol. II, 1913-1949 (Box 64, Folder 298)
  - SIGMA LAMBDA KAPPA
    See:
  - SIGMA XI
    - Diploma (Folder 1C)
  - SKULL AND BONES
    - John E. Kimball, 1865 (Box 68, Folder 320)
  - SOPHOMORE GERMAN COMMITTEE
    - Secretary"s book, 1911-1917 (Box 68, Folder 321)
  - ST. ELMO CLUB
    - Yearbook, 1922 (Box 68)
  - STUDENT COUNCIL
    - Senior Council, 1908-1910 (Box 69, Folder 322)
    - Minutes, 1921-1927 (Box 69, Folder 323)
    - Report, 1920 (Box 69)
    - correspondence, 1923-1928 (Box 69, Folder 324 - 325)
    - Checkbook, 1925 (Box 69, Folder 326)
    - Bank statements, 1928 (Box 69)
    - Report on Educational Organization, 1927-1928 (Box 69, Folder 327)
  - THETA NU EPSILON
    - Lambda Epsilon Chapter: constitution and member list, 1870 (Box 70, Folder 328)
  - THULIA BOAT CLUB
    - Constitution, members and minutes, 1853-1854 (Box 70, Folder 329)
  - TORCH AND MASK SOCIETY
    - Historical records, minutes and members, 1879-1889 (Box 70, Folder 330)
  - VARUNA BOAT CLUB
    - Captain"s book of records, 1860-1867 (Box 78, Folder 382)
  - WICKET CLUB
    - Records, 1850 (Box 78, Folder 383)
  - THE WIGWAM
    - Constitution and by-laws, 1900 (Box 78, Folder 384)
  - WOODEN SPOON
    - Presentation Address: John E. Kimball, 1857 (Box 78, Folder 386)
    - Songs, 1869 (Box 78)
  - WURTS DEBATING CLUB, SCHOOL OF LAW
    - Records (Box 78, Folder 387)
  - YALE AMATEURS
    - Invitations and responses, 1933-1934 (Box 78, Folder 388)
  - YALE REPUBLICAN CLUB
    - Constitution and minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 90, Folder 461)
    - Minutes and miscellaneous material, 1966-1967 (Box 90, Folder 462)
    - Correspondence
      - A-C, 1965-1967 (Box 90, Folder 463)
      - D-G, 1965-1967 (Box 90, Folder 464)
      - H-L, 1965-1967 (Box 90, Folder 465)
      - M-P, 1965-1967 (Box 90, Folder 466)
      - Q-s, 1965-1967 (Box 90, Folder 467)
      - T-Z, 1965-1967 (Box 90, Folder 468)
      - Internal, 1966-1967 (Box 90, Folder 469)
      - Miscellaneous, 1965-1967 (Box 90, Folder 470)
      - Miscellaneous, 1965-1967 (Box 91, Folder 471)
    - Press releases, 1966-1967 (Box 91, Folder 472)
    - Newsletters, 1966-1967 (Box 91, Folder 473)
    - Newsletters: state and national, 1965-1967 (Box 91, Folder 474)
    - Newsclippings, 1966-1967 (Box 91, Folder 475)
    - Membership lists, constitution, and addresses to the club, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder 476)
    - Printed material, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder 477)
    - Printed material: assorted, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder 478)
    - Posters, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder 479)
  - YALE UNION CLUB
    - Notebook: list of members, 1864 (Box 93, Folder 481)
  - YALE UNIVERSITY BOAT CLUB
    - Minutes of meetings, 1873-1896 (Box 93, Folder 482)
  - YALE UNIVERSITY CLUB
    - Minutes, 1916-1933 (Box 93, Folder 483)
    - Constitution, mortgage, deeds, charter, and insurance policies, circa 1900-1932 (Box 93, Folder 484)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, receipts, and records, circa 1910-1931 (Box 94, Folder 485)
    - Notices See also: Yale Clubs Folio #1 (Box 94, Folder 486)
    - Notices (Folder 1B)
  - YORK STREET CLUB
    - Records, 1856 (Box 94, Folder 487)
  - ZETA PSI
    - By-laws, 1937 (Box 94, Folder 488)
- Yale clubs and organizations, 1834-1975; Accession 19ND-A-378
  - A.P. SOCIETY, CLASS OF 1839
    - Constitution and records, 1836-1837 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - NATURAL HISTORY SOCIETY
    - Minute book, 1834-1857 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Constitution, rules of order, scattered minutes and papers from meetings, 1834-1841 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1835-1837 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1838-1842 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Subscription lists, 1835-1836 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Donation list, 1836-1841 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Treasurer"s cash book, 1835-1841 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Treasurer"s reports and account books, 1838-1857 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Bills and receipts
      - 1835-1837 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - 1838-1844 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - 1857-1860 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Lists, printed forms, and miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - YALE OUTING CLUB
    - Minutes of meetings, Trips, lists of members, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - YALE CHESS CLUB
    - Notes and clippings compiled by Percival Robertson Y 1912 S, 1909-1912 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - BOOK AND GAVEL SOCIETY
    - Papers gathered by Charles P. Shernan (1896) [Yale Law School Society], 1897-1916 (Box 2, Folder 16 - 17)
  - BETA THETA PI
    - The Covington Trust: financial report, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - YALE ITALIAN SOCIETY
    - Constitution, 1924 March 12 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - TEMPERANCE SOCIETY
    - Records of the Temperance Society of the Class of 1843, 1840 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - ALPHA SIGMA PHI